guys about wearing any comma mark I'm
wearing an augur hoody though I'll have
auger
I got great merch all right up to this
sculpey I don't know is it broken
all right we can't go inside the office
anymore
this is working I can't see my followers
a49
wow we have so much followers okay we
can't go inside the office anymore
because honestly guys there's too many
secrets in the office there's too many
secrets everywhere you look there's a
secret
look here like Here I am on the hood of
my Accord if you look carefully there's
actually a secret in the image right
like there's secrets everywhere
um but what I am showing you all today
yeah
bra bra look I shaved bras yeah all
right look this is a a super-secret see
like I can't go anywhere without there
being secrets look at this this is a
super secret your dad your ass super
secret oh look at that secret I'm glad
you guys are enjoying open pilot we love
to have you on board with the comma army
if you guys saw the label article it
makes me so happy
not that way most doing badly I'm not
happy that way Mo's doing badly I'm
happy that the truth is being revealed
all the maps I told you I'll show you
the maps last time we can't go inside
guys there's just all that I said this
is a current monitor this is a USB
current monitor so we just can make sure
that it's outputting enough current you
walk the EON and you can get a sticker
who said stickers would be included if
you show me where terrible I don't know
let's go in the back let's go in the
back you guys want to say highness go
peace
yeah yeah well say I don't look at that
shit
yeah check out our Cadillac guys we're
pivoting we're pivoting to light are
unspinning light are all this law we
need Wi-Fi outside I think we did an
Access Point outside just for the scope
is on the comet tree is that banner I
think we even have worse cell reception
it's so terrible look at the comet tree
look at the comet tree up there it's
beautiful I can't even watch it it's
working look at the beautiful comet ray
no we just don't have good reception but
you know we wanted to show you look we
have line ours and then to solid state
light ours the line aren't you know
maybe the lighter is using the Wi-Fi no
I switched to sell congrats George light
ours the smart you guys we're trolling
you only this car has lidar and it's to
calibrate and validate our maps okay
we're proving that our maps are how
accurate 10 centimeters that's right
that's right because if we don't use
lidar we can't show you how accurate our
maps are to 10 centimeters no no no no
lidar for validation purposes only on
this beautiful Cadillac especially these
solid state light arts they work great
all right guys umm if we didn't see it
we're gonna take a quick look at the
Hyundai Santa Fe and this is just a hype
scope II don't worry we're not really
using lighter we're not gonna make you
know what's that light our costs that
things are twenty five thousand dollars
twenty five thousand well let's look in
here look you can see 3d printers oh
what's plugged into the Panda oh that's
a USB current monitor but this scope is
all that hype and that's most of it you
guys saw the hype we got lidar on our
Cadillac that I touched the light are
good lidar alright this is our this is
our hand i Santa Fe
hopefully the quality is a little bit
better now that I will leave you guys
right in the Santa Fe look at that yeah
anyone looks kind of funny
that's crazy Eon yeah right
no that's crazy yeah look at that II
know that's crazy Wow crazy yo all right
bro yeah I know right ladders so
expensive you want us to use ladder now
if you thought eons were expensive at
$6.99 which by the way get in bye bye
bye no no no this is a this young case
yeah I'll just I'll just show you guys
look look look at look at the craziness
oh look at that beautiful shit all right
I'm sorry about the lag yeah yeah yeah I
know just when you guys are seeing
secrets
where are the maps real Oleg you know
exactly when the maps are coming out you
know exactly when they're coming out we
have some more stock not too much though
eons are gonna run out and probably like
a little under a month at the current
rate um no STL file come on I'll give
you the STL file all right let's just
I'm just gonna will leave the last scene
of the periscope will be me touching the
lidar thank you thank you look good
lighter good light are good lighter you
cost you cost one quarter of an
employee's salary for a year good
lighter oh okay bye vice Covey's all
hype